<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Software Freedom Day 2014</title>
    <description>Software Freedom Day is celebrated all around the Globe</description>
    <link>http://openosk.github.io//</link>
    <atom:link href="http://openosk.github.io//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>SFD BLOG</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Was it because I did not sleep for more than few days that I was not able to sleep when I had
free time? Or was the day an exciting one that stole my sleep, that I am sharing this wonderful
experience with you?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;sfds-success&quot;&gt;SFD’s success&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First day of call for finding a sponsor for SFD’14 we head out towards our country’s most
reputed companies. In just few working days each and every team, that were categorized were
working hard for SFD’s success. The art team were just wonderful, they were free and ready to
volunteer for other teams as well. Amazing when we found that they are ideal and yet we have
no task to ask them to do. Just minutes before you ask something, they were right their standing
with the final design that is waiting to be praised, totally professional. In One word AMAZING!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;noisiest-web-team&quot;&gt;Noisiest Web Team&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The web team were the noisiest ones they were everywhere, but seeing all the volunteers on the
division was quite surprising, never had I seen a group of members working vigorously to
achieve a goal of what they had never heard of. Their determination and effort to make SFD’14 a
success is complete praiseworthy. Having such a hard time adapting to a new environment we
had volunteers from web group helping us manage SFD as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;guffadi-in-group&quot;&gt;Guffadi in group&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite the bad starting of the day, with speeding ticket at early morning, losing a pen drive and
few bucks we had a wonderful day. This was only possible with the highly professional guffadi in
the group. This might have been the reason why we had completely forgotten about the alerts
that our empty stomach was sending us. However, dressing up as an IT expert or any advocates
with mere few rupees in our pocket, and in a limited time frame, we managed to print all required
documents, proof read it, and planned how and where to go. We were ready to give back to the
community.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;new-members-not-focused&quot;&gt;New Members not focused&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The handful of volunteers from the all categorized group, were strapped in their seat to take off
for top business house of the country. Sadly, we had only a new yet an active members in the
club, as we lacked on moving on time. We regret that we didnot focus on new members of
NOSK which might have been the reason why we failed to include them in the trip.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;lost-in-nosk&quot;&gt;Lost in NOSK&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a team of six and our “mama” we took off from NCIT. Soon after we made an exit from the
entrance of NCIT we realized the traffic, and then discussion began, “hya dai, kasto jam,
shortcut bata jaam.” , Driver Dai replies, “cha ni tara jhan time lagna sakcha”. Those were the
last words I remember as we were working of filing the documents to specific business houses.
After working through the files, I was completely blank and had no idea where we were is when I
shared, “Last bhok lagiracha yaar, department store bata Fast food khaedim hai?”, Turning to
Surit I asked him “Surit, Timile khayou?” not realizing that we were working together from the
beginning of the day. At that very moment Prakash shared “Dai, ma sutekai chaena, hijo raat
bhari jekyll ko documentation padera kta haru lai aja sikaye”, “Ani maile dui din padera php ko
exam pani diyeko thiye”.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;finishing-retardiness&quot;&gt;Finishing Retardiness&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ani Prakash Course ko pani esari padhna sakchau?” I asked. We all laughed with what he said.
Then I heard the new enthusiastic one from the back seat, seemed like he had no clue what we
were up to. That face of his was totally priceless, not knowing why he felt awkward we made him
feel comfortable among us by taking him to every venue us as he had to learn everything. Then
we divided ourselves into two groups and then visited those major companies that we planned.
After distribution of the letters we headed towards our college. Overall we had a wonderful time
and that is what NOSK members are working on, uniting and creating friendship among young
enthusiastic programmers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;any-questions&quot;&gt;Any questions?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Email organizers at &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#105;&amp;#110;&amp;#102;&amp;#111;&amp;#064;&amp;#110;&amp;#111;&amp;#115;&amp;#107;&amp;#046;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#103;&amp;#046;&amp;#110;&amp;#112;&quot;&gt;&amp;#105;&amp;#110;&amp;#102;&amp;#111;&amp;#064;&amp;#110;&amp;#111;&amp;#115;&amp;#107;&amp;#046;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#103;&amp;#046;&amp;#110;&amp;#112;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 14:45:00 +0545</pubDate>
        <link>http://openosk.github.io//blog/call-for-papers</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://openosk.github.io//blog/call-for-papers</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello World</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;SFD wiki page and our Team has been registered in SFD website. Further, teams are allocated for Web Designing, Entertainment, Art Work and for management.
Preparations regarding celebration were initialized and assigned respective responsibilities. Management team visited many organizations and colleges for sponsorship and invitation. 
Art team designed awesome flyers, stickers, news letter and banners. Web team with enthusiasm and hard-working been able to code smoothly.
With the encouragement and curiosity, entertainment team were able to collect all the open source 3D-movies, photo booth, etc. 
Open Art team are ready and excited to make people art instantly. Here we are ready and eager to celebrate Software Freedom Day on 20th September.
So, please do join us at Nepal College of Information Technology(NCIT), Balkumari, Lalitpur.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 13:45:00 +0545</pubDate>
        <link>http://openosk.github.io//blog/hello-world</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://openosk.github.io//blog/hello-world</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
